So this is shortly after Alex Preddy had been savagely unalived by ICE.
And in the comments on this video, I said, you know,
flying an American flag in this moment is a special type of Stockholm syndrome.
And of course, a white woman felt the need to say,
go away, you're not from Minnesota.
Stop criticizing people who are mourning.
Be negative somewhere else, Amanda.
Not today, not here.
Yes, today, every day, everywhere.
I will remind you people what this nation has always been.
You're mourning?
I'm a black person.
I've never not been in mourning in this nation.
I came into the world mourning.
Y'all are mourning?
Flying, flying that flag for many of us has always been a slap in the face because it
has never represented for those of us what it represents for you.
You're in mourning?
No shit.
You're so blown away by what's happening because it's just now happening to white people.
This has been happening.
So don't tell me when and where I get to remind you of the goddamn truth of this nation.
If anything, I better remind you at the sight of this nation doing what it's been doing and
expanding that so that you can maybe continue to be a force to stop it because you should have been
a force to stop it a long time ago.
Again, shout out to Minnesota.
Standing up and standing tall and standing loud.